Bob Ross: Happy Accidents, Betrayal & Greed is a
documentary film directed by Joshua Rofé.
Bob Ross brought joy to millions as the world's most famous art instructor.
But a battle for his business empire cast a shadow over his happy trees.
Self (archive footage), played by Bob Ross.
Self - Bob's Son, played by Steve Ross.
Self - Bob's First Wife, played by Vicky Ross.
Self - Artist and Friend, played by John Thamm.
Self - Assistant Professor, Georgetown University, played by Ian Bourland.
Self - Art Historian, played by Julia Friedman.
Bob Ross: Happy Accidents, Betrayal & Greed is a 2021 American biographical documentary
film produced and distributed by Netflix and directed by Joshua Rofé.
The film offers a look into the life and career of painter and television
host Bob Ross, and the battle for his business empire.
The film was released on August 25, 2021.
The film explores themes of artist, painter, lawsuit, business ethics, cancer.
The tone is thought_provoking.